Where the hell're you goin'?!
C'mere, you damn mutt!
Wait, you damn mutt!
Don't run off with my EXP!
Draconic Buster.
That puts me at level 18.
I... I can't.
I can't do this after all.
Kobato!
What are you doing spacing out?
You'll get killed.
Oh, Ikusaba-san...
It's Asagi.
I'm always saying how much I hate
being called by my family name.
If you're doing it on purpose,
then 70 percent of the girls
in class will ostracize you.
I-I'm sorry.
Yeah, I forgive you!
Listen, there's something I wanna
confirm with our harmless little pigeon.
What? Oh, um, sure.
If I'm reading things right,
our class is probably gonna fall apart.
Huh?
I mean, it's full of big egos,
you know what I'm saying?
A lot of them are a pain, too.
And to make matters worse, we've been
assigned ranks like S-Class and E-Class.
Oh, by the way, I'm a B-Class.
In due time, distinct factions
are going to splinter off for sure.
When that happens...
of course you'll be joining mine, right?
Won't you?
As a D-Class, you won't make
it into Kirihara's group.
And the Takao sisters are always a pair.
Ayaka... is just going to die anyway, y'know?
What? Sogou-san will?
Wh-What do you mean by that?
You don't get it, huh?
At any rate,
Kobato-chan, you should think long
and hard about where you stand.
Depending on how things play out,
if we manage to defeat this
Great Demon Empire and return to our world,
then what we achieve here
could affect us back home,
and you might find yourself
with nowhere to fit in, Kashima Kobato-chan.
Even if your abilities suck,
I can always make good use
of these in a pinch, after all.
So let's do our best together, little pigeon.
Now with that...
Bring it out, girls!
That's...
Our sweet little pigeon hasn't yet cleared
the test the goddess assigned us, right?
So we're gonna help you out.
The Asagi group is all going
to get stronger together.
So hurry up and kill it.
Or do you want to be
disposed of like Mimori?
Hurry up!
Good job, little pigeon!
You've passed the test,
and that settles things!
Now you're one of us too, little pigeon.
Mimori-kun...
Don't worry.
I won't abandon you.
I'm sorry. I couldn't do anything.
I...
Mimori-kun!
ENCOUNTER ~AVENGER(S)~
- Pity what happened with Sir Tooka Mimori.
- I'm so sorry,
but that ritual is a firm policy
of the Kingdom of Alion.
You have my deepest apologies, Miss Sogou.
No way...
However, you don't have
time to wallow in sadness.
The ritual is still ongoing.
These past few days,
while you've been sleeping away,
everyone else departed on a test
to determine if they can kill a monster.
However, several have failed to take up arms
against the monsters and been disqualified.
And we must ask that those who cannot
fulfill their duty as heroes take their leave.
You mean to cull the weak?
That is Alion's policy.
Let me be clear, Goddess.
Go right ahead.
Please speak your mind.
I do not agree with the
way you're doing things.
Well, the world is full of all sorts
of people and opinions.
As a goddess, I am tolerant of all.
So I'm willing to brook
a slight difference of views.
That said, we must dispose of the worthless.
It's unfortunate.
An S-Class hero is valuable to you, right?
Yes! Extraordinarily so.
Then I'll do my duty as an S-Class hero
to make up for the students
who couldn't clear your test.
If I do that, will you call off
their disposal?
My, how courageous!
What a wonderful proposal!
I'd expect no less of an S-Class hero!
Now then, let us shake
hands in reconciliation.
I do apologize for punching
you in the stomach,
even if it was to settle your hysterics
over the unusual nature of your situation.
I have high hopes for you, Miss Sogou.
Right.
What cold hands...
THE DARK FOREST
I thought I'd finally given them the slip!
"THE SWORD GOD" MAGATS BLAYDIN
- Still trying to run, huh?
You can conceal your presence,
but you suck at hiding, Princess Knight!
"THE OUTLANDISH DEMON" ASHURA
- You can conceal your presence,
but you suck at hiding, Princess Knight!
"SUPER PRESSURE" JIOBANE SENGAI
- Should we reap her already?
Don't be stupid!
The foreplay's just getting started!
The least she can do is give us a little fun.
Right, Zarash?
"THE FANG" ZARASH FINEBARD
- We'll have to start by carving
the truth into her soul.
That any attempt at escape or resistance
is futile against us, the Holy Watchers.
THE HOLY WATCHERS
- That any attempt at escape or resistance
is futile against us, the Holy Watchers.
THE HOLY WATCHERS
Now then...
Stats: Open.
TOOKA MIMORI
LV 1,789
- Only my MP is exceptional.
TOOKA MIMORI
LV 1,789
- But what I want to confirm now is...
But what I want to confirm now is...
I can dismiss Paralyze at will.
On just the head, too.
I can also dismiss Poison
or make it nonlethal.
Guess I can avoid killing targets that way.
Maybe I'll try it out if
there's a monster nearby.
Next...
I need a blade.
A sword.
Someone who can act as a tank
and handle the frontline for me.
Are those...
slimes?
Don't let them get away with that.
I guess that's that...
That's the spirit!
Paralyze.
Poison.
POISON (LETHAL)
- So I can change the setting from here, huh?
POISON (NONLETHAL)
- I see.
- And this option dismisses it?
PARALYZE (DISMISS)
Get lost.
I made it so you can't move,
but I'm about to undo that.
Don't worry.
I have no intention of killing you.
Though I am going to say
something kinda haughty.
Sorry for not helping you sooner.
But, well, you did good.
It was nice to see you stand
up for yourself against them.
Don't attack me once you can move, okay?
PARALYZE (DISMISS)
Later.
Have a nice life.
Well, damn.
You planning to keep following me?
I see.
You're an outcast just like me, aren't you?
They're far away.
But their presence still lingers.
They're just waiting
for me to exhaust myself.
So this is how the Holy Watchers
of heroic blood hunt...
Can you see behind me?
Good. Now I have eyes in the back of my head.
Befriending you was the right move.
Here we are.
I see. A forbidden art, huh?
I guess it would be.
An experiment to strengthen monsters...
It even describes how to craft
a solution to enhance slimes.
Anglin was probably afraid
of this being misused.
Hey.
What I'm after is plain
old personal vengeance.
I'm on a journey to that end.
So you'll be going along with my ego.
Are you okay with that?
If you want out, now's your chance.
Hmph, I see.
Then I'll be counting on you, Piggymaru.
That's your name.
But if you have any objections,
I'm listening.
PIGGYMARU
SLIME
Forbidden magic and arts...
I'll use anything I can
to crush that goddess.
I will get my revenge.
They've closed the distance.
I really can't shake them!
I guess I'll have to use it.
What I seek is the regalia of spirits.
By our pact,
I offer thee my sleep as payment...
Silfigzea,
Ferillbanger,
Willozega!
Spirit Regalia!
Hmm?
Who's this? He sure ain't the girl.
Wh-Who are you?
Some mangy brat?
The mere sight of you disgusts me.
Well, for now, go ahead
and drop all your valuables.
Then we'll spare your life.
No, we're killing him.
I haven't tested this baby's edge
on a living human yet.
So I'll try it out on this sack of trash.
If you are, then make it quick, Magats.
The girl should be running
out of stamina soon.
The nice thing about men is there's
no wasting time enjoying them first!
Not much fun in abusing 'em
before we kill 'em.
Let's hurry up and catch the woman so we
can use the money at Ablom's brothel.
Better yet, let's grab a good-looking
girl from a nearby town
and drag her around for half a year
while we have fun breaking her.
Screw you!
No woman's ever lasted half a year
when you set out to break her!
Shut up!
It's their fault for losing it so fast.
Honestly, having our way with
that woman would be the best course.
Man, I won't be satisfied with human
women after laying eyes on that bitch!
Even so, we have to refrain from taking
advantage of our prey this time.
Remember who paid for this job.
So, where do you think you're going,
trying to back away in fright?
Please...
P-Please just let me go!
I don't want to die here for nothing!
I told you you're out of luck.
I'll test this out on you quick,
then we have to get back to work.
- So go right the hell ahead
and fall victim to me, Magats!
- Paralyze.
Wha—
Good.
My status ailment skill
is effective on humans, too.
I guess that damn goddess
is the only exception.
Impossible!
You're not as intimidating
as the monsters in the ruins.
Though I guess your malice is
equal to or worse than theirs.
I'm saying you're all scumbags.
You're mad too?
Of course. Well, it's not going to bother me
if these guys die.
In fact, I think I'll feel better.
Meet bloodlust with bloodlust.
Meet hostility with the same.
In short, it means I can kill.
Even facing humans, I can kill.
Poison.
You can feel it too?
Yeah, I know.
There's someone else nearby.
Their presence is gone?
They're not moving?
Are they plotting something?
No, I can sense someone.
What is this feeling?
Their presence isn't terribly strong,
but it's unsettling.
The spirits are frightened of it.
Paralyze.
I sensed your intent to attack,
but there's something else
mixed in with your hostility.
It got me curious.
So I thought we could chat for a bit,
though I'm keeping you
immobile as a precaution.
What... are you after?
Well, I seem to be lost.
I'm not from around here,
so I'm not familiar these parts.
I was hoping you could help fill me in.
And the other four...?
Are they friends of yours?
Not at all...
I'm going to let you move your mouth now.
If you try anything funny,
I'll use my skill again.
PARALYZE (DISMISS)
- I'm bluffing.
- I have means of hurting you, too. Got it?
PARALYZE (PARTIAL DISMISSAL: HEAD)
- It's impossible to stack Paralyze.
- I have means of hurting you, too. Got it?
PARALYZE (PARTIAL DISMISSAL: HEAD)
- Though I didn't exactly lie.
- Understand?
PARALYZE (PARTIAL DISMISSAL: HEAD)
- Yes...
I-I can speak normally now?
Your mouth is all you can move.
Sorry, but I'm still wary of you.
I went through a lot on my way here,
so I don't readily trust strangers.
There is something I wish to confirm
before I answer your questions.
Did you encounter a group of four?
I did.
Where are they now?
I killed them.
What? You killed them?
Is that a problem?
No, but you slew the Holy Watchers...
Don't tell me you did it all by yourself.
Or do you have other allies nearby?
Just one.
Though I don't intend
to reveal them at the moment.
Thank you for humoring me.
I sensed no falsehood when you
claimed to have defeated those four.
- I know you have answered me faithfully.
- She seems extremely confident
in her ability to discern lies.
I will also answer your questions
as honestly as I can.
You are my savior after a fashion, after all.
You don't seem like a bad person to me.
So far.
Does that mean I've earned some of your trust?
A little.
But like you, there are things
I'd rather not talk about.
So I think it's best if neither of us
pries too much.
Yes, I would be grateful for that.
Okay, then it's my turn to ask questions.
I see...
So this isn't Alion.
It's a forest in the south
of the Kingdom of Ulza.
I just assumed the Ruins of Disposal
were in Alion.
One last question.
Do you know anything about this writing?
This... I believe it's ancient script.
A rather unique variation, too.
Can you read it?
No, I'm afraid I cannot.
I see. Okay.
I'll just have to research it the hard way.
However, I might know someone who
should be familiar with that writing.
She was once known as the Witch of Taboos.
She possessed such vast knowledge
of the forbidden in this world that
she was deemed dangerous.
I heard she was driven
from her homeland.
If I wanted to find her, where should I go?
The Land of Golden-Eyed Monsters.
Land of Golden-Eyed Monsters?
It's a treacherous heartland of the continent.
Thank you for the valuable tip.
I cannot say I've repaid my debts.
After all, you saved my life.
No, you can say we're even.
So now we'll be parting ways.
That's fine by you, right?
Y-Yes.
As long as you're satisfied.
She's got a real sense of honor.
For better or worse, she's too honest.
She reminds me of my aunt.
She was so nice that it
made me worry about her.
I-Is something the matter?
No. You'll be free in a few minutes,
but I can't guarantee your
safety until then.
I understand.
I'll be released soon enough.
Yeah. This may not mean much
after I ambushed you,
but I'll pray for your safe travels.
Yeah. It's not like I take
any delight in slaughter.
I won't resort to pointless murder.
I only kill in accordance with my own rules.
I can't deny the possibility
that woman will come after me
to attack me once she's free to move.
So keep watching my back.
I'm counting on you, partner.
That's a helluva bounty, ain't it?
They say she was a paladin of Neah,
which got wiped out by Bakoss,
and that she's the princess of that old
half-elf nation too, you know.
If some ruffians captured
her for the bounty,
you think they'd hand over such
a beauty without having a taste?
Anyone would want to try
fooling around with her.
That Seras Ashrain.
THE WOMAN KNOWN AS THE PRINCESS KNIGHT